Finding Aid for the John Cope Caldwell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John Cope Caldwell Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0066
18.9 linear_feet
INDEX JOHN COPE CALDWELL
This is a name index of the correspondents of John Cope Caldwell. The figure (or figures) in parentheses immediately following each name denotes the total number of letters from that person in the collection; the dates are for the time of the letters. The last number given refers to the box in which the correspondence may be found. ( See Index Number 2.)
A
Abbott, Faith, (17); Jan. 24, 1956, Aug. 23, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, Sept. 24, 1956, Apr. 15, 1957, Aug. 5, 1957, Aug. 13, 1957, Oct. 21, 1957, Nov. 6, 1957, Jan. 20, 1958, Feb. 18, 1958, Jan. 8, 1959, Jan. 15, 1959, Jan. 16, 1959, Feb. 25, 1959, March 27, 1959, n.d.; 4
Abstine, James, to William H. Bowman, (1); Feb. 24, 1956; 4
Adams, Betty, (1); Dec. 6, 1962; 4
Adams, Marie, (1); May 30, 1962; 4
Ahlers, Margaret A., (1); Nov. 18, 1952; 4
Akins, Cheryl, (1); May 14, 1962; 4
Aley, Ruth, (7); Apr. 14, 1953, Apr. 21, 1953, June 16, 1953, Oct. 8, 1953, Feb. 19, 1954, Apr. 2, 1959, n.d.; 4
Allen, Clifton J., (2); Apr. 24, 1956, Mar. 25, 1957; 4
Allen, Jane, (1); Jan. 28, 1963; 4
Allerbury, Daisy, to Alfred Kohlberg, (1); May 6, 1955; 4
Allison, Anne, (1); Mar. 18, 1953; 4
Aluvihare, Deryck, (5); Oct. 9, 1959, Nov. 7, 1959, Jan. 27, 1960, Feb. 12, 1960, Apr. 7, 1960; 4
Alvarez, Robert S., to Ralph Wheatley, (1); Apr. 28, 1954; 4
Ament, Jack, to Lee Keedick Lecture Bureau, (1); Sept. 20, 1951; 4
Anderson, Carolyn, (1); Aug. 13, 1964; 4
Anderson, Janet, (1); Mar. 26, 1962; 4
Anderson, Mitzi, (1); Sept. 30, 1959; 4
Anisimov, Oleg, (1); Apr. 29, 1953; 4
Anthony, Joseph, (1); Jan. 22, 1954; 4
Appelbaum, Howard, (1); May 10, 1966; 4
Arculli, Robert, (28); Mar. 28, 1956, July 24, 1956, Oct. 23, 1957, Apr. 2, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 27, 1959, May 12, 1959, June 8, 1959, July 29, 1959, Mar. 11, 1960, Mar. 27, 1960, June 17, 1960, July 23, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept. 24, 1960, Sept. 28, 1960, Oct. 7, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Nov. 20, 1960, Dec. 26, 1960, Dec. 30, 1960, Jan. 17, 1961, Mar. 16, 1960, Oct. 12, 1961, Oct. 24, 1961, Oct. 31, 1961, June 7, 1962, n.d.; 4
Arens, Richard, (2); Oct. 4, 1956, Jan. 31, 1957; 4
Armesto, Felipe F., (1); Apr. 26, 1955; 4
Arthur, William B., (1); Sept. 23, 1954; 4
Asbury, William F., (1); Oct. 31, 1953; 4
B
Baddour, Frank M ., (1); Aug. 15, 1959; 4
Bahnsen, Elaine, (1); Jan. 14, 1963; 4
Bailey, James L., to Frank Bass, (1); Feb. 14, 1951; 4
Bain, Gordon M. (1); Apr. 17, 1959; 4
Baker, E. C., (1); July 27, 1964; 4
Baker, Harold, (1); June 3, 1953; 4
Baker, M. E., to Lee Keedick, (1); Nov. 18, 1953; 4
Baker, Margaret, (8); Dec. 29, 1956, Jan. 10, 1957, July 15, 1957, Sept. 13, 1957, Feb. 2, 1959, Apr. 13, 1959, Nov. 19, 1959, Jan. 3, 1962; 4
Baker, Mary E., (3); n.d.; 4
Baldridge, John D ., (1); Sept. 26, 1950; 4
Baldwin, Faith, (1); n.d.; 4
Balgooyen, H. W., to Alice Widener, (1); Nov. 23, 1956; 4
Ball, Ernest C., (1); May 23, 1955; 4
Ball, Gloria M., (1); June 6, 1962; 4
Balls, H. O. to Enio Eva, Juan Panayotti, Gilberto H. Aguirre, Juan Parodi, Jose Rodriquez, Cesar Morales, Jose M. Maetinez, and Jose Figueres, (8); June 26, 1954; 4
Baran, Nicholas M., (1); Mar. 6, 1963; 4
Barker, Clothilde, (1); Apr. 19, 1955; 4
Barrameda, Fred, (2); Nov. 3, 1959, June 17, 1960; 4
Barrett, Reginald, (1); Feb. 18, 1959; 4
Barrette, Elise D., (1); Aug. 19, 1957; 4
Barry, William F., (1); Oct. 24, 1952; 4
Bartlett, Carrie, (1); Sept. 20, 1952; 4
Bass, Frank E., (1); Aug. 21, 1951; 4
Bass, James P. (1); Sept. 22, 1960; 4
Bass, W. A., (1); Nov. 12, 1956; 4
Bates, Mary N ., (1); May 19, 1955; 4
Baxter, Charles M ., (1); Sept. 19, 1956; 4
Beaman, Lucy M ., (1); Mar. 22, 1957; 4
Beard, Mary L., (1); n.d.; 4
Beck, Dewey M., to Lee Keedick, (1); May 29, 1951; 4
Beckman, Richard W ., (1); Nov. 28, 1951; 4
Benarfa, Florence V., (1); Oct. 4, 1955; 4
Bennett, E, H, (2); July 30, 1952, Aug. 8, 1952; 4
Bennett, Josiah W ., (2); Nov. 18, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953; 4
Benson, George S., (1); Jan. 4, 1957; 4
Benson, George S./ to Forrest F. Reed, (1); Dec. 4, 1956; 4
Bentley, Frank R. (1); June 9, 1959; 4
Beresford, Donald C., (2); Jan. 22, 1963, Feb. 7, 1963; 4
Berman, Sanford, to .John Day Company, (1); July 3, 1960; 4
Berrean, Sally, (1); July 5, 1956; 4
Berry, Loren M., to Thomas A. Burke, Alexander Wiley, and "Friend", (3); May 18, 1954; 4
Bess, Demaree, (1); June 5, 1959; 4
Bevis, Palmer, (4); June 23, 1953, July 9, 1953, Aug, 3, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953; 4
Bey, Betty, (1); July 11, 1956; 4
Bibb, Mary, B. (1); Apr. 24, 1955; 4
Bierly, Ivan R., (2); Nov. 29, 1956, Dec. 28, 1956; 4
Billing, Mabel S., (1); Oct. 28, 1953; 4
Blancly, Frederich J. 0., (3); Mar. 6, 1958, Mar. 22, 1957, Apr. 14, 1958; 4
Blake, Betty, (2); Nov. 10, 1958, Apr. 4, 1961; 4
Blake, Helen L., (1); Dec. 13, 1953; 4
Blochloger, Edna M ., (1); Jan. 22, 1961; 4
Blossom, John D., to Lee Keedick, (1); June 25, 1951; 4
Blossom, John D., (2); Aug. 27, 1951, May 14, 1952; 4
Boekel, William A. (1); Feb. 18, 1957; 4
Booth, Audrey J., (1); Feb. 11, 1953; 4
Bosley, (3); Mar. 3, 1958, Oct. 22, 1958, Nov. 14, 1958; 4
Botter, David, to Lee Keedick, (2); Feb. 17, 1955, July 11, 1955; 4
Boughton, W. E., (1); Sept. 30, 1959; 4
Bouman, Loenard F., (1); July 27, 1959; 4
Bouscaren, Anthony T., (5); Feb. 10, 1956, Feb. 23, 1956, Mar. 13, 1956, Apr. 4, 1956, Sept. 21, 1955; 4
Bowden, Joan, (1); Nov. 10, 1955; 4
Boyce, Ralph L. (2); July 6, 1955, Nov. 24, 1959; 4
Boyce, Ray, (1); Sept. 13, 1955; 4
Boyd, Louise W ., (1); Oct. 14, 1952; 4
Bradshaw, Ruth, (1); Nov. 15, 1960; 4
Brandt, Claudia M ., (42); Sept. 23, 1959, Nov. 20, 1959, Mar. 4, 1960, May 25, 1960, June 1, 1960, June 2, 1960, Aug. 31, 1960, Sept. 19, 1960, Sept. 27, 1960, Oct. 3, 1960, Oct. 5, 1960, Oct. 11, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Jan. 12, 1961, Mar. 13, 1961, Apr. 20, 1961, July 18, 1961, Sept. 8, 1961, Sept. 21, 1961, Sept. 21, 1961, May 4, 1962, May 8, 1962, May 9, 1962, May 16, 1962, May 23, 1962, Junel, 1962, June 14, 1962, Aug. 29, 1962, Sept. 18,. 1962, Dec. 4, 1962, Dec.7, 1962, Feb. 28, 1963, Mar. 18, 1963, May 22, 1963, Dec. 4, 1963, Jan. 3, 1964, Jan. 10, 1964, Jan. 20, 1964, Feb. 3, 1964, Feb. 3, 1964, Feb. 12, 1964, Feb. 14, 1964, July 23, 1964, Aug. 19, 1964; 4
Brandt, P. W ., (1); Sept. 20, 1960; 4
Braniff, Ronnie, (1); Mar. 2, 1966; 4
Brannon, C. T., (1); May 24, 1963; 4
Branscomb, Harvie, (2); Sept. 18, 1952, Oct. 2, 1952; 4
Breed, Joseph B., (1); Feb. 12, 1954; 4
Brent, Ruth, (1); Mar. 18, 1956; 4
Brewster, Harold N., (1); Apr. 17, 1956; 4
Brewster, Dorotyh, (1); n.d.; 4
Bricker, Ralph 0., (1); Mar. 24, 1952; 4
Briggs, Thomas J ., (1); Nov. 26, 1956; 4
Brines, Russell, (14); Sept. 21, 1955, Oct. 11, 1955, Nov. 16, 1955, Nov. 23, 1955, Jan. 31, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Oct. 19, 1956, Nov. 30, 1956, Dec. 13, 1956, Jan. 3, 1957, Aug. 7, 1957, Aug. 13, 1957, Nov. 20, 1957, Dec. 10, 1957; 4
Brisk, Fay, (2); Mar. 12, 1958, Mar. 18, 1958; 4
Brockway, George P., to Ruth Aley, (1); June 20, 1951; 4
Brockway, George P., (1); Jan. 28, 1954; 4
Broker, Warren. (17); May 26, 1954, June 2, 1954, June 9, 1954, June 25, 1954, Oct. 12, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954, Oct. 28, 1954, Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 26, 1955, Mar. 30, 1955, Apr. 15, 1955, Apr. 26, 1955, May 31, 1955, Aug. 3, 1955, Sept. 16, 1955, Oct. 4, 1955, Dec. 12, 1955; 4
Brooks, Linda, (1); Feb. 15, 1965; 4
Brown, E. Robert, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr., (1); July 1, 1959; 4
Brown, E. Robert, (1); Aug. 21, 1959; 4
Brown, Norman N., (3); Dec. 26, 1960, Dec. 30, 1960, Jan. 23, 1961; 4
Brown, Wallace O., (1); May 23, 1956; 4
Browne, R. A., to Richard Walsh, Jr., (1); July 8, 1965; 4
Browne, Robert B., (1); July 8, 1952; 4
Bryan, June E., (1); June 13, 1952; 4
Bryce, Allan D., (1); May 6, 1963; 4
Buck, Pearl S., (1); Mar. 5, 1956; 4
Buckley, Maureen L., (1); Mar. 7, 1958; 4
Buckley, Pricilla L., (1); May 5, 1959; 4
Buckley, William F., (7); Jan. 30, 1956, Feb. 28, 1956, July 18, 1956, June 28, ;957, Apr. 1, 1959, July 28, 1959, Nov. 19, 1959; 4
Budlong, M. V., (1); Mar. 5, 1952; 4
Budoyo, Sri, (1); Nov. 25, 1959; 4
Bunis, N. J ., (1); Jan. 30, 1953; 4
Bunker, Patricia, (4); Sept. 9, 1955, Aug. 16, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Nov. 24, 1956; 4
Bunster, Yolanda, (1); Nov. 24, 1960; 4
Buol, Susan P., (6); May 25, 1955, Jan. 29, 1960, July 20, 1960, Aug. 16, 1960, Aug. 18, 1960, Dec. 1, 1962; 4
Burke, Arleigh, to D. D. Hanson, (1), Feb. 20, 1959; 4
Burton, William F., to Civiv and Church and Auxiliary Groups and Clubs, (1); n.d.; 4
Burke, Coleman, (2); Sept. 16, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958; 4
Burrell, Elsie, (1); n.d.; 4
Burris, Miriam, (1); Mar. 31, 1960; 4
Bussard, Paul, (1); Sept. 30, 1953; 4
Butler, George N., (1); Apr. 25, 1963; 4
Butler, Joan, (12); Nov. 9, 1964, Nov. 11, 1964, Dec. 7, 1964, Dec. 8, 1964, Jan. 6, 1965, Jan. 12, 1965, Feb. 5, 1965, Mar. 5, 1965, Aug. 20, 1965, Dec. 2, 1965, Dec. 13, 1965, Dec. 20, 1965; 4
Buttinger, Joseph, (1); Oct. 2, 1959; 4
Byrd, Valdis, (1); Sept. 21, 1960; 4
C
Caldwell, Elsie, (1)7 n.d.; 4
Caldwell, Harry, d)7 Apr. 28, 1955; 4
Caldwell, John, d)7 n.d.; 4
Caldwell, Kenny, (1)7 n.d.; 4
Calkin, K. N ., (1); Oct. 23, 1952; 4
Callahan, North, (2); Apr. 15, 1956, June
Camesas, Theodora, (1); Mar. 24, 1959; 4
Camp, Richard W ., (1); Aug. 16, 1951; 4
Capon, Norma J., (1); Dec. 18, 1957; 4
Carder, Clyde D., (1); Apr. 15, 1960; /4
Carland, John E., (1); Sept. 29, 1955; 4
Carman, J. A., (3); Jan. 13, 1964, Jan. 16, 1964, Feb. 28, 1964; 4
Carnall, William H., to Loretta Reidy, (1); Sept. 21, 1955; 4
Carothers, Neil, (1); Apr. 17, 1953; 4
Carson, D. D., (2); July 18, 1958, Jan. 28, 1959; 4
Carter, Helen, (5); Aug. 4, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Aug. 5, 1954, Nov. 30, 1954, n.d.; 4
Carter, Juliet R., (1); n.d.; 4
Cartwright, Frank T ., (5); Mar. 12, 1952, June 9, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954, June 8, 1955, Sept. 21, 1962; 4
Case, Lillian T., (1); Jan. 16, 1953; 4
Cassiday, Bruce, (1); July 20, 1955; 4
Cazzulino, Arthur, (1); Oct. 31, 1960; 4
Celliers, Peter J., (3); Oct. 30, 1952, Nov. 23, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954; 4
Chadwick, C. S., (1); Jan. 5, 1952; 4
Chamberlain, William, (1); May 21, 1955; 4
Chang-huan, Shan, (1); Jan. 12, 1955; 4
Chen, Terry T. L., (1); Sept. 21, 1956; 4
Chennault, C. L., to Velma N. Tate, (1); Aug. 19, 1957; 4
Chennault, C. L., (1); Sept. 5, 1957; 4
Chih-Mai, Chen, (18); Sept. 9, 1954, Sept. 18, 1954, Oct. 22, 1954, Nov 28, 1954, Jan 3, 1955, Jan. 4, 1955, Jan. 7, 1955, Apr. 25, 1955, May 4, 1955, May 25, 1955, June 1, 1955, July 14, 1955, July 21, 1955, Aug. 3, 1955, Aug. 22, 1955, Nov. 18, 1955, July 9, 1956, Oct. 9 1956; 4
Ching-Kuo, Chiang, (2); n.d., Dec. 26, 1953; 4
Chodorov, Frank, (3); June 18, 1954, June 24, 1954, July 21, 1954; 4
Chow, E. H., (3); Aug. 13, 1953, Aug. 25, 1954, Feb. 27, 1956; 4
Christian, James W., (1); Aug. 19, 1960; 4
Chun, Sung C., (1); May 9, 1959; 4
Cimbolo, Salvatore, (1); May 4, 1962; 4
Clark, Howard, to Virginia Cain and Forrest F.. Reed, (2); May 15, 1953, May 28, 1953; 4
Clark, Howard, (33); May 13, 1953, May 27, 1953, June 2, 1953, June 8,, 1953, June 16, 1953, June 19, 1953, June 22, 1953, July 1, 1953, July 8, 1953, July 21, 1953, July 21, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Sept. 29, 1953, Jan. 14, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Feb. 15, 1954, May 7, 1954, July 15, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 12, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Oct. 4, 1954, 0ct. 6, 1954, Oct. 14, 1954, Oct. 14, 1954, Dec. 23, 1954, Jan. 4, 1955, Apr. 28, 1955, Sept. 8, 1955, Nov. 9, 1955; 4
Clark, William A., (1); June 24, 1953; 4
Clarke, Helen, (1); May 28, 1956; 4
Clarke, J. Calvitt, to Richard Walsh, Jr. and John T. Gibson, (5); Mar. 26, 1956, June 1, 1956, Aug. 28, 1956, Sept. 5, 1956, Nov. 26, 1956; 4
Clarke, J. Calvitt, (6); Apr. 25, 1955, Apr. 12, 1956, May 28, 1956, Apr. 20, 1959, n.d.; 4
Clarkson, Helen, (3); Jan. 15, 1958, Jan. 23, 1958, Feb. 6, 1958; 4
Clement, Frank G ., (1); May 20, 1966; 4
Close, H. M. C., (1); Nov. 6, 1957; 4
Cochrane, Joanna, (1); Nov. 13, 1957; 4
Cohen, Donna R., (1); June 5, 1952; 4
Cohn, Roy M ., (1); Mar. 3, 1953; 4
Coillie, P., (1); n.d.; 4
Colclough, Elizabeth S., (5); June 13, 1951, June 18, 1951, June 21, 1951, June 29, 1951, Mar. 6, 1952; 4
Coleman, Hara L., (1); n.d.; 4
Coleman, J. Winston, to Forrest F. Reed, (1); Mar. 18, 1955; 4
Collado, Jose' Moguel, (1); May 2, 1963; 4
Coller, Edward W., (5); Oct. 7, 1952, July 14, 1954, Mar. 22, 1955, July 22, 1956, Sept. 8, 1957; 4
Collins, Louise E., (1); Feb. 10, 1956; 4
Combs, Betty, (2); Jan. 23, 1959, n.d.; 4
Conlon, Edward J, (3); Sept. 15, 1958, Jan. 27, 1959, Feb. 25, 1959; 4
Conrad, Bettye, (1); n.d.; 4
Conway, Peggy, (1); n.d.; 4
Cook, Jim, (1); Mar. 11, 1957; 4
Cook, Maude H ., (1); Oct. 7, 1952; 4
Cool...., Monaca, (1); n.d.; 4
Cooley, Bernard H ., (1); Aug. 14, 1953; 4
Cope, Quill E., (2); Nov. 5, 1956, Nov. 9, 1956; 4
Copeley, Helen M ., (2); May 22, 1953, Mar. 23, 1956; 4
Cornuelle, H. C., (2); Mar. 12, 1953, Mar. 20, 1953; 4
Corrigan, Kevin, to Pyo Wook Han, Walter L. Seaman, and Anson C. Lowitz, (3); July 25, 1952, Oct. 22, 1952, Feb. 26, 1953; 4
Corrigan, Kevin, (38); June 24, 1952, July 25, 1952, Sept. 10, 1952, Sept. 17, 1952, Sept. 23, 1952, Oct. 2, 1952, Oct. 10, 1952, Oct. 17, 1952, Oct. 20, 1952, Oct. 22, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, Oct. 30, 1952, Nov. 12, 1952, Nov. 13, 1952, Nov. 18, 1952, Nov. 18, 1952, Nov. 20, 1952, Nov. 21, 1952, Dec. 5 1952, Dec. 11, 1952, Dec. 30, 1952, Jan 2, 1953, Jan. 5, 1953, Jan. 9, 1953, Jan. 16, 1953, Jan. 20, 1953, Jan. 22, 1953, Jan. 23, 1953, Feb. 9, 1953, Feb. 23, 1953, Feb. 25, 1953, Feb. 26, 1953, Apr. 6, 1953, May 4, 1953, May 19, 1953, June 9, 1953; 4
Courtenay, Walter R., (1); Dec. 20, 1952; 4
Coverdale, J. S., (2); Mar. 22, 1957, June 3, 1957; 4
Cowan, L. W ., (3); Aug. 22, 1960, Sept. 6, 1960, Nov. 2, 1960; 4
Cox, Helen, (1); Feb. 19, 1960; 4
Crafts, Ralph, (1); Oct. 9, 1956; 4
Craipain, G. M ., (1); Aug.13, 1959; 4
Crawford, Paul, (1); Nov. 15, 1955; 4
Cromelin, Marie A., (1); May 6, 1963; 4
Cronin, John F., (3); Oct. 13, 1955, Oct. 19, 1955, Nov. 9 ,1955; 4
Crooks, Thomas E., (3); May 22, 1957, June 14, 1957, July 3, 1957; 4
Crossman, Julie.,- (4); May 24, 1954, June 15, 1954, July 12, 1954, Aug. 17, 1954; 4
Crounse, Laura H., to Elizabeth Schenk, (3); Feb. 4, 1953, Mar. 4, 1953, May 18, 1953; 4
Crounse, Laura H., (5); Feb. 4, 1953, Feb. 17, 1953, Apr. 5, 1953, Jan. 25, 1957, n.d.; 4
Crowe, Thomas G. (4); Feb. 8, 1954, Feb. 17, 1954, Mar. 16, 1954, Sept. 17, 1956; 4
Cutwell, Hugh, (1); n.d.; 4
D
Daly, Gerald R., (2); Nov. 20, 1950, Jan. 18, 1951; 5
Daly, Thomas F. (10); July 3, 1957, July 10, 1957, July 15, 1957, Aug. 1957, Aug. 12, 1957, Aug. 19, 1957, Aug. 27, 1957, 10, 1957, Sept. 12, 1957, Oct. 9, 1957; 5
Daniel, Marjorie L., (1); Feb. 5, 1955; 5
Dank, Leonard D., (1); Nov. 1, 1960; 5
Dashiell, Alfred S., (1); Sept. 3, 1954; 5
Daumarie, Y ., (1); Jan. 27, 1959; 5
Davies, Susan A., to Lee Keedick, (1); Nov. 19, 1954; 5
Davies, Thurston, (2); Dec. 19, 1950, Nov. 4, 1953; 5
Davies, William, (1); Dec. 25, 1956; 5
Davis, Louise, (1); Mar. 22, 1960; 5
Davis, Malcolm, (1); Dec. 23, 1957; 5
Davis, Robert, (1); Aug. 3, 1952; 5
Day, John, (2); Oct. 13, 1961, Aug. 17, 1966; 5
de.Beausset, Connie, (1); Mar. 21, 1954; 5
Debo, Angie, (1); Mar. 29, 1954; 5
de Grosbois, Roly, (1); Dec. 12, 1963; 5
DeJong, George, to Christian Herald Editor, (1); n.d.; 5
De Vault, Doris, (3); July 5, 1957, Apr. 2, 1960, July 7, 1961; 5
Dewire, Ethel, to Loretta Reidy, (1); Oct. 26, 1955; 5
Dewire, Ethel, (1); Nov. 5, 1955; 5
Delaney, Robert F., (1); May 24, 1963; 5
Dell, Joan, (1); Nov. 10, 1953; 5
Dey, Robin, (1); Apr. 2, 1956; 5
Dick., Sarah, (2); July 6, 1962, Aug. 18, 1963; 5
Dixon, Jeanne T., (1); Oct. 29, 1953; 5
Dodd, Margaret, (2); Feb. 8, 1963, Feb. 20, 1963; 5
Donlevin, Robert, (3); May 4, 1954, June 3, 1954, June 25, 1955; 5
Donner, Francine Me, (1); Oct. 19, 1956; 5
Donovan, Thomas J., to Haller Lewis, (1); July 3, 1959; 5
Dorn, Frank, to Henry Regnery, (1); July 23, 1953; 5
Dorn, Frank, (1); July 24, 1953; 5
Doss, Lilyan, (1); n.d.; 5
Dowling, William J. to Reader’s Digest, (1); Jan. 9, 1957; 5
Dowling, William J ., (1); Jan. 31, 1957; 5
Dozier, Daisy, (1); Dec. 10, 1957; 5
Draper, John L., (1); July 8, 1952; 5
Dresser, Amos, (1); Feb. 10, 1954; 5
Drew, Charles W ., (1); Nov. 12, 1959; 5
Du Buque, Jean H., (1); July 2, 1959; 5
Due, Nguyen Phu, (1); June 30, 1959; 5
Dudleston, Joseph, (2); June 2, 1959, Mar. 26, 1964; 5
Duff, J. Arthur, (2); Jan. 7, 1963, Jan. 19, 1963; a. 5
Dugdale, Grant, (3); Mar. 3, 1955, Mar. 7, 1955, Mar. 22, 1955; 5
Dumasia, Behram P., (2); Jan. 29, 1960, Sept. 2, 1960; 5
Duncan, Gorgan B., (1); Feb. 6, 1953; 5
Dunlop, H. P., (1); July 5, 1951; 5
Dunn, Thomas, (1); July 31, 1965; 5
Duvall, Jo, (1); July 22, 1955
E
Early, Robert P., (1); June 24, 1954; 5
Edmonds, Mildred, (6); Dec. 11, 1956, Nov. 30, 1956, Jan. 31, 1957, Oct. 21, 1957, Nov. 19, 1957, Dec. 31, 1957; 5
Edwards, Clyde S., (1); June 18, 1952; 5
Egger, Patt, (1); Oct. 7, 1955; 5
Einhorn, Rose D ., (1); Dec. 3, 1959; 5
Einhorn, Paula, (1); Sept. 26, 1961; 5
Eisenhower, Dwight D. (1); Sept. 7, 1956; 5
Eldridge, Kenneth T ., (1); Mar. 16, 1965; 5
Eliot, T. S., to Charles Lowry, (1); Dec. 12, 1956; 5
Ellinwood, Margery L., (1); Oct. 15, 1951; 5
Elliot, James A., (2); Aug. 17, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, 5
Elliot, Norman K., to Mrs. George E. Maynard, (1); May 8, 1956; 5
Elliott, William Y., to Charles W. Lowry, (1); Aug. 5, 1957; 5
Ellis, C. M., to Lee Keedick and Loretta Reidy, (2); Oct. 10, 1950, June 21, 1958; 5
Elmguist, Ruth M ., (2); Nov. 16, 1953, Nov. 20, 1953; 5
Embry, Carlos B., (1); Aug. 4, 1956; 5
Engebretson, Rae, (4); Apr. 18, 1955, Jan. 27, 1959, Mar. 14, 1960, n.d.; 5
English, James W., to Richard Walsh, (1); May 21, 1956; 5
English, James W ., (1); July 15, 1955; 5
Epstein, Albert S., (2); Mar. 8, 1957, Apr. 1, 1957; 5
Erman, Dick, (2); Apr. 24, 1955, n.d.; 5
Ernst, Philip W ., (1); May 3, 1963; 5
Eton, Suh, (1); Nov. 4, 1952; 5
Evans, Helen F., (2); Apr. 16, 1951, Apr. 25, 1951; 5
Ewald, Barbara, (1); May 28, 1962; 5
Ewing, Anne 0., (1); n.d.; 5
Ewing, Cornelia K., (1); n.d.; 5
Eyestone, J. Bruce, (1); Feb. 4, 1954; 5
Eyre, Dean J ., (1); n.d.; 5
F
Fagen, Beverly, (1); Mar. 1, 1965; 5
Fahmy, Susan D., (1); June 8, 1956; 5
Fallis, William J., (1); Jan. 4, 1955; 5
Farolan, M ., (1); Oct. 19, 1959; 5
Fawcett, Eugenia, (9); Oct. 28, 1953, Oct. 19, 1954, Nov. 26, 1954, Jan. 26, 1955, Mar. 1, 1955, Apr. 1, 1955, Apr. 6, 1955, May 5, 1955, June 25, 1957; 5
Federico, Grace, (4); Sept. 17, 1965, Dec. 7, 1965, Dec. 9, 1965, Dec. 15, 1965; 5
Feldman, Harvey, (1); Aug. 26, 1954; 5
Felt, George E., (1); Mar. 22, 1963; 5
Fenton, R. W ., (1); Jan. 8, 1962; 5
Fideler, Raymond E., to Richard J. Walsh, Jr., (1); Feb. 11, 1959; 5
Fielder, Gerald L., to Saturday Evening Post, (1); Sept. 5, 1961; 5
Finnely, John W ., (1); Oct. 23, 1952; 5
Fisher, Dorothy C., to Lesley, (1); June 3, 1953; 5
Fisher, Ralph H ., (1); Sept. 26, 1950; 5
Fitzgerald, Roy G., (1); Nov. 29, 1957; 5
Fitzpatrick, Thomas F ., (1); May 18, 1954; 5
Flanagan, Francis D., (1); Feb. 27, 1953; 5
Flanagan, John C, (1); Mar. 31, 1959; 5
Flanigan, J. P,, to Janet Schoelles, (1); Oct. 24, 1952; 5
Fleischman, Merlene, (1); Mar. 26, 1961; 5
Fletcher, Archie G., (3); Apr. 27, 1954, Feb. 4, 1959, Sept. 26, 1959; 5
Fletcher, Donald R., (5); Sept. 20, 1960, Nov. 17, 1960, Jan. 23, 1961, June 14, 1962, n.d.; 5
Fletcher, Martha, (1); Jan.4, 1954; 5
Floyd, Louise P. (7); Sept. 2, 1953, Sept. 23, 1953, Sept. 29, 1953, Oct. 5, 1953, Oct. 7, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953, Oct. 23, 1953; 5
Floyd, Robert L., (2); Aug. 16, 1952, Aug. 20, 1952; 5
Fockler, Shirley, (5); June 21, 1960, Jan. 2; 1963, Jan. 24, 1963, Mar. 18, 1954, Mar. 30, 1964; 5
Fogle, Cindy R., (1); Mar. 28, 1962; 5
Forbes, Sally, (1); Mar. 14, 1961; 5
Fore, William F., (1); Feb. 16, 1959; 5
Forrestal, James, to Elsie I. Fletcher (Caldwell), (1); Feb. 17, 1946; 5
Foschini, Bernard M., to Father Mannion, (1); Aug. 2, 1957; 5
Foschini, Bernard M., (8); Dec. 12, 1956, Dec. 26, 1956, Dec. 30, 1956, Jan. 11, 1957, Aug. 2, 1957, Aug. 16, 1957, Aug. 24, 1957, Dec. 5, 1957; 5
Foster, Donald C., (2); Oct. 8, 1959, Oct. 26, 1959; 5
Foster, Paul, (1); July 16, 1959; 5
Fowler, David M ., (1); July 27, 1953; 5
Fowler, Virginia, (1); July 21, 1955; 5
Frank, Helen, (1); Nov. 30, 1964; 5
Frankenhoff, Laura B., (1); Apr. 28, 1959; 5
Franklin, Charlotte, (1); May 31, 1962; 5
Franks, Maurice R., (4); Jan. 17, 1955, Feb. 21, 1955, Apr. 21, 1955, Apr. 27, 1955; 5
Frazier, Bernard W ., (1); Jan. 26, 1959; 5
Frey, Joseph R., (1); June 22, 1951; 5
Frillmann, Paul W ., (1); Mar. 15, 1956; 5
Frost, Lesley, (1); n.d.; 5
Fulton, Jane, (1); Mar. 3, 1958; 5
Fu-sung, Chu, (4); Aug. 2, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Dec. 12, 1956, Dec. 22, 1956; 5
G
Gade, Wallace A., to George Johnston, (1); Sept. 27, 1956; 5
Galub, Jack, (4); May 13, 1959, May 26, 1959, June 10, 1959, June 11, 1959; 5
Gamby, Ray, (1); May 30, 1959; 5
Gammon, James P., (1); May 28, 1948; 5
Gantz, Shirley, to John Day, (1); Apr. 6, 1960; 5
Garcia, Louise, (2); July 10, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960; 5
Gardner, Dorothy B., (1); Sept. 6, 1956; 5
Gardner, John, (1); Oct. 9, 1952; 5
Garside, B. A., (1); Feb. 14, 1959; 5
Garvey, Neil F., to Lee Keedick, (1); July 16, 1952; 5
Garvey, Neil F., (2); July 11, 1952, July 16, 1952; 5
Gaucher, A. Ernest, (1); Feb. 25, 1957; 5
Gaudion, D. A., to Elizabeth Schenk, (1); Nov. 9, 1950; 5
Gault, Alma E., (2); Oct. 14, 1953, Nov. 25, 1953; 5
Gay-Tuff, E., (2); Mar. 19, 1955, Sept. 30, 1955; 5
Gdams, Uniola, (1); Jan. 1, 1958; 5
Gebhardt, Irene, (1); Jan. 26, 1954; 5
Geppert, G. E., (1); Mar. 16, 1951; 5
Gibson, Ellen, (1); Sept. 15, 1960; 5
Gibson, John T., to James Michener, (1); July 9, 1957; 5
Gibson, John T., (14); Oct. 17, 1955, Sept. 21, 1956, Dec. 31, 1956, Feb. 1, 1957, Feb. 20, 1957, Mar. 7, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 6, 1957, May 20, 1957, July 12, 1957, Aug. 2, 1957, Oct. 22, 1957, Feb. 2, ,1959; 5
Gibson, Russell, to U. S. A., (1); Dec. 28, 1957; 5
Giga, Seiji, (3); Aug. 18, 1958, Sept. 9, 1958, Nov. 12, 1958; 5
Gil, Lois M ., (1); Sept. 12, 1955; 5
Giles, Lewis, (1); Jan. 30, 1959; 5
Girson, Rochelle, (1); Sept. 27, 1960; 5
Glass, Carter, to Ralph Wheatley, (1); June 16, 1954; 5
Glass, Mildred D., to Reader's Digest, (1); Mar. 4, 1957; 5
Glover, Fay W ., (4); May 14, 1963, Aug. 23, 1963, Oct. 13, 1964, Sept. 28, 1965; 5
Goldberg, Hy, (1); Jan. 2, 1955; 5
Gomane, Andre', (1); n.d.; 5
Goodfellow, M. Preston, (1); July 29, 1953; 5
Gordon, Horace, (1); Jan. 9, 1958; 5
Gossard, J. Earl, (1); Apr. 6, 1955; 5
Gossett, Jane, (1); Nov. 6, 1956; 5
Gouffe, N. F., (2); Jan. 8, 1963, Jan. 16, 1963; 5
Gould, Randall, (3); June 16, 1952, Feb. 21, 1954, n.d., 5
Graeser, Mary L., to Sir, (1); Dec. 10, 1956; 5
Graham, Eleanor, (1); May 19, 1960; 5
Gras, Gloria, (2); Feb. 22, 1955, Mar. 21, 1955; 5
Gregersen, Magnus I., (5); Dec. 12, 1955, Oct. 10, 1956, Dec. 5, 1956, Feb. 25, 1957, n.d.; 5
Green, George F., (1); May 17, 1955; 5
Green, Var M ., (1); Feb. 28, 1968; 5
Greene, Adron, (2); July 9, 1959, Sept. 25, 1959; 5
Greene, John L., (2); Apr. 21, 1955, May 6, 1955; 5
Greene, M. C., (2); June 5, 1956, Aug. 2, 1956; 5
Greene, Mary V., (1); May 25, 1953; 5
Greenfield, Margarette, (1); Oct. 22, 1957; 5
Grisson, Alice, to Lee Keedick, (1); Nov. 15, 1953; 5
Gronenberg, Rubert H., to John Day, (1); Feb. 6, 1951; 5
Grossman, Frances, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr., (1); Nov. 12, 1958; 5
Gruver, Kate E., (3); Mar. 9, 1956, Apr. 19, 1956, Feb. 26, 1957; 5
Gunn, Henry M ., (1); Sept. 5, 1957; 5
Gutke, Audrey, (1); June 5, 1959; 5
H
Hagan, Dorothy S., (1); Jan. 8, 1958; 5
Halden, Frahk C., (1); Apr. 27, 1954; 5
Hall, Clarence W ., (15); Aug. 6, 1953, Aug. 11, 1953, Aug. 14, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, Oct. 21, 1955, Mar. 20, 1956, May 2, 1956, Oct. 3, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Dec. 7, 1956, Dec. 14, 1956, Feb. 13, 1957, Mar. 4, 1957, Jan. 20, 1958, Jan. 20, 1958; 5
Hall, Mary, (1); Aug. 24, 1965; 5